Hello.
Oh, like 2030.
Yes.  Where are you from?
Stavropol.
Cool.  My father is from Mineralnye
Vody.
Super.  What does 2030 mean?  What is this?
This is the administrative reform of Russia by
2030.  Reform project.
Well, at least I met one adequate person
in 45 minutes.  There is an
open day at the kindergarten today.  Maybe at
school, I still don’t understand.  You are also the
first adequate one I have come across.  I've been
sitting here for an hour now and I was thinking about losing my
temper.   Where are
you from?
I am from the city of Khmelnitsky.
Oh, how.  And
what kind of Khmelnitsky buns are these?  This is the first time
I've heard of it.
You're near the computer,
right?
Now google the network of
Khmelnitsky
buns bakeries.   All over
Russia there are Khmelnitsky buns,
coffee shops, and bakeries.
Stavropol.
So, Bakery, yes, there are Khmelnitsky
buns in Stavropol.  What a joke.
All over Russia this is a network card.  And you did
n't know.
What is the topic?  What are they in honor of?
Wait, but you too, as I understand it, are an
entrepreneur or what do you do?
Entrepreneur.  But in our city of
Khmelnytskyi there are no Khmelnytskyi buns.
So, why did you have this in your city
[laughter]? It was
enough in other cities?
No, I'm just wondering why they're
called that?  Maybe you have some city in
Stavropol, a town called Khmelnitsky
.  Ah, well,
I’ll tell you this, you’ll probably find
this information interesting.
Ah, I was involved in patenting,
patents, in short, for trademarks,
brands, and so on.  And in our city and in
general throughout our region and in other regions,
in Krasnodar, in Rostov, there was a
chocolate shop.   There is
actually a family that
opened a chocolate shop.
Leonid, this is Leonid Leonidovich Glushchenko
Khmelnitsky.  This is the founder of just a
factory.  Okay, got it.
Yes, but the fact itself, I was very
surprised now, because I didn’t know that
such a city existed or that it was a
populated area.   Do
you get this from Ukraine?
From Ukraine, yes.  And this is a city named in
honor of Bohdan Khmelnytsky.  That is, there was
such a commander Bohdan Khmelnytsky.   That
's where the surname Khmelnitsky comes from, it's
common there, and the
city of Khmelnitsky was named in his honor.  Now I
see, yes, that in Stavropol in
1995, in the basement of the Stavropol
Agrarian University, he opened a bakery
.
And yes, there was a brand called Khle.
And now we have, well, so you understand, we have a
whole, yes, so to speak, a
large block, a whole district.  And in the whole
area there are
about 10 of these points, maybe more in one
area.
In short, the Ukrainian Glushchenko-Khmelnitsky,
yes, kind of bakes bread for you there, right?
M.
Amazing baked goods, cakes,
different types of bread.
Understood.
Well, I have never eaten tastier bread anywhere.
What do you do?  What do you bake in
life?
I work on the radio.  I am the Head of
B2B and B2C Sales at Smag.
Cool.  So you're selling advertising?
Well, it’s not even like we just sell advertising.
We, in fact, today, with
all our circumstances, are acting
as a lifesaver for our
business, because we create a buzz
around every enterprise.  That is, we can
carry out our task individually.  Whether
it's launching an ad in one format
or taking complete control of all
promotion.
But if, for example, well, I think
you have such cases often now, yes,
that, uh, the Wberries warehouse is on fire, yes, and
the entrepreneur needs to quickly
sell the remaining stock from another warehouse, yes,
because they know that in a couple of days
that warehouse will also burn down.  Were you approached and did you
promote such things?
We cannot promote such things simply
because they
do this promotion here via the Internet.  asking
his audience for support.
The Internet works much better
because if we work specifically for a specific
target audience or location, then here the
Internet spreads throughout the entire
country of Russia and then goes further.
Well, yes, I understand.
Therefore, for these entrepreneurs,
this call will be more
contextual.  My friends approached me personally
.  I generally never
sell them anything that people don’t need.  This is my
sales principle, so to speak.  And,
accordingly, I said: “Guys,
go online, release 10, 20, 30,
40, 50 videos on Instagram a day.”  But
you have to cover the whole of Russia,
so that... I
mean, I understand, that is, you can
only advertise local,
for example, second-hand on the street there,
in short, Mineralnye Vody, yes,
for example, like this?
No, we can cover the entire
Stavropol Krai of the Caucasian Mineral Waters, which includes
more than twenty cities and villages.
Or we can even assist in
your context.  That is, we have a
system called Kenera - it is an artificial
intelligence that manages social networks
and unites nine platforms.
Holy [ __ ],
this is a really cool system.
I understand.  I still won't
order it because I'm from Ukraine.
This is it.  So what's it all about?
I'm just telling you that we're not just
local, that is, we work here with
all of Russia and in general.  Understood.  So what are
you even talking about here?  What
attracted you to chat roulette?
Oh,
tell me, how can I address you?
Andrey Vasilyevich,
I am still older than you, I am 45.
Well, not that much older.  Just a
15 year difference.
Well, 15 years is still, you know, when I
finished school, you hadn’t gone to nursery yet
.
Yes, but in your situation, men
have exactly these kinds of mistresses.  So,
Andrey, my name is Alexandra.
According to.  Understood.  You are already laying claim to your
mistress, but we are somehow in different
jurisdictions.
Mm,
I only enter into relationships with girls
from Ukraine.  I enter into relationships
only with girls from Ukraine.
Well, it's clear that we do
n't quite agree here.  But if we
return to the question of what
exactly I am doing here, I think you
understand me, because you are in the
same circumstances.  There are
times when you want
to talk to someone, but you don’t want anyone nearby,
or you don’t want anyone from your
circle close.  Yes.
Accordingly, you go to some
open sources where you can find
more interesting people from other countries,
cities, the
CIS, and so on.  And we can chat about
life or understand.  You know, I'm here for
myself, why do I go on chat roulette? Yes,
for example, I work a lot, I'm in
business, yes, and then in the evening
I want to disconnect.  And so, you know, when
you’re traveling on a train and you have some fellow travelers in your compartment
with whom you talk about
everything and nothing.  And you understand, in an
hour or two you will get off at different stations and that’s it
, no
, and it’s easy for you to talk to them.  I
also use chat roulette for this kind of
internal relaxation.
For daddy,
yes, for daddy.  Here you are my
ass today.
I interpret it that way too,
[clears throat]
right?  You see, there are two of us in our compartment
today, right?  And we established a connection in
conversation.
Well, we are just very
hard-working people, so we were able to
afford to buy two
months at once.
Well, yes, in our case,
yes, I immediately assessed you as soon as you entered the
compartment.  I immediately realized that you are a very
hard-working girl.
[laughter]
That's great, Andrey.  Well,
how should we address you?
And I introduced myself.   I
guess I missed it.  We men are
usually inattentive.
Yeah.
Well, probably yes.  You are Andrey, and I am
Alexandra.  Yuryevna is possible, but without
formality.   Let's do it this way
.  After all, there is a 15 year
difference between us.  Let me call you Sasha
.
Alexandra.
Alexandrochka.
Shurochka.
Alexandra.
This is so fundamental.  Alexandra.
Well, I don’t claim to be your mistress,
so for you today I’m
Alexandra.   Wow
.  I would be scared if
you applied for the position of mistress.
But imagine if I came
into your office to negotiate for the sole
reason that I wanted to cooperate with you.   I have a
gag reflex when it comes to Russian women.
[laughter]
Seriously?
[laughter][sighs heavily] No
one has ever told me that before.
No, well, let's say I weren't
Russian.
Ah, well then it would be a different matter, yes, if
you came to me, there was a Ukrainian, a
Georgian, an Estonian.
No, wait, we'll figure it out now
.  You have a reflex towards
Russians, but nevertheless you are interested in
talking to me?  Yes, well, to communicate, yes,
but, let's say, to enter into some kind of connection,
yes, so that I could touch you, so that you could
touch me, so that I, God forbid, could
immerse my, let's say, male dignity in
your inner world.  No, that's what I... No,
wait, that wasn't what we were talking about.
I just asked you a question.  Imagine,
I come to you to collaborate.  That's right, I
don't want any cooperation.  So,
to talk like this through chat roulette, yes,
as if remotely, yes, when it’s
like coronavirus, that it doesn’t spit on
you, it’s not transmitted, yes.  It's still possible.  But in
person, well, let's say, it would be a
bit of a hassle for me, I'm honest, I'm an open
man, yes, I don't like to beat around the bush, I speak
straight to your face.  I would be uncomfortable
talking to you in person.
Andrey, well, look, given the
circumstances, I accept your
position, but you must clearly understand
that you are
also flying over my house.
Yes, I know.
And in my yard,
my son plays football in exactly the same way.
And I feel absolutely nothing for you,
but I feel absolutely nothing for your location
.  I communicate with you
without any pretensions or gag
reflex.
Well, look,
only then the moment is different.   Yes.
What are we afraid of, Andrey?
I will say this without fear.  I'm with a psychiatrist,
right?  I have a personal psychiatrist.  I am a
psychologist by education.
No, this is a psychiatrist.  Yes.  The thing is that
since 2022,
since 2014, I have started to develop
some kind of aversion to Russian women, yes.
Here.  And since 1922 there has simply been some kind of
, let’s say, physiological
rejection.  I talked to a psychiatrist, yes,
we work with him now once a
week, I come to the reception on Saturdays
.  We spend about 45 minutes, yes,
and I work through it, yes, he
shows me photos, yes, he says: “
Look, girl, uh, which one do you
like.”  I'm showing it.  She says,
"Oh, she's Georgian."  This shows: "Do
you like this girl?"  I say: "Yes,
very cool."  She says: "She is
Russian."  And I just have, you know, well
, some kind of internal reflection
that I liked the girl, she’s
Russian, you know?
May I ask a modest question?
Yes, you can.
Given your age,
were you previously in a relationship with a
Russian woman, years ago, or perhaps there
was some kind of romantic encounter?
No, the Belarusian once did, but the Russians
don't.
Maybe you just subconsciously
want a Russian woman?
Well, you know, that's how it is, yes,
circumstances, you can't
afford it.
Possibly, possibly.  You know, I’m
latent, and this latent one is, you know,
some kind of Russophile, right?  Perhaps I am
some kind of latent Russophile, perhaps
I want such perversions, yes, but
my upbringing, my male
nature, does not allow me to show these.
And have you not considered that you need to
work through this with someone other than a psychiatrist?  I think
that through certain circles you can
pick up a Russian woman and do whatever you want with her
.  The only question is:
how far will your imagination go?  After you
stand there, you will understand what the fact was.
Look, fantasy.  Well, if I were to
pick up a Russian woman, I have a ton of imagination
, but the Criminal Code of Ukraine,
unfortunately, prohibits me from realizing my
fantasies, right?  That is, what I would like to
do to a Russian woman is
punishable by 15 years to
life imprisonment.
But you and I are no different
from each other.  You and I speak absolutely the
same language.
Absolutely absolutely identical.  Yes, that's what I'm
talking about.  But as for my fantasies,
look, when I see a
beautiful girl from Ukraine, from Poland, from
Estonia, yes, I immediately have some kind of - well,
like a healthy man, some kind of
emotional attraction.  When I see a
Russian woman, yes, I was even
abroad last year and saw them
on the streets, and I, sinfully,
start having bad thoughts, yes, let's say
she's like a Georgian in this.  I just don’t
know, I don’t control these emotions.
Honestly, that’s why I work with psychiatrists
.  I don't know.  I saw, did you
see that video of a Georgian guy at a
wedding who ran up to those Russian women
who were pouring something on the wedding and
pulled it up her nose?  When I saw this, I had some kind of
internal
emotional orgasm, you know?  I just
realized the dream of
many, many people.  In fact,
when I saw this video, it was
initially presented as if he
simply burst into the room and beat up our
girls, and then from the surveillance cameras and
so on they began to refute all of this, saying that the
girls behaved themselves.  There were
very nice people sitting there,
celebrating.
Honestly, even I, a Russian, would
knock down such a Russian woman
if she were ruining my holiday.
It's a
mess, yes.
So that's how it is
, yes, look, you
will understand me.  I have the same situation, yes,
look, the Russians are now ruining the life of
my country, yes, my children and so
on, yes, and I have the same thing.  I
just, I don’t know, maybe you’re a good
Russian woman, maybe you’re against the war, I don’t
know, but you see this attitude in me
.  I am against war.  I
lost my friend in the very first days of
the war.  We have a siren flying over my house
.  We are far from you.  We are
Stavropol Krai.  Maybe you should see
where you just typed in
Stavropol.
I am very afraid for tomorrow.  And I do
n't blame anyone.  I just live in it.  And
I try to know how long
I am supposed to live.  I want to live this out in goodness and
joy.  Honestly, I have no contempt for
anyone.
Certainly.  Listen, I'm telling you, I do
n't have any contempt for Russians either, but for some reason,
when I see news about a drone flying
into a marketplace in Samara or an oil refinery in
Yaroslavl or hitting a house somewhere over there
,
and here in Stavropol it crashed into
Neminoma.   There was
no fire in Neminomysk.  Listen, I
posted it directly on my Facebook and said:
"This is God's punishment, you know?
I'm from
Nevinamysk."
Everything there simply burned down.
Yes, my friend almost died there.  I
don't feel anger even in connection with such
events.
Damn, how are you going
to tell me this straight?  And you from
I just remembered those burning warehouses.
Honestly, it inspires me
when I see that, uh, the war has come from
Ukraine back to Russia, I get a
thrill from it.  I even get
excited by this somehow, yes.  You know, even though you are
Russian, yes, and I want you, but,
probably, perhaps, against the backdrop of the burning
Kremlin, I would have this, this would have
excited me, you know, so that
Moscow would have been reduced to ashes, to radioactive ashes, yes, and I, in short, you, you
know, for this, you know, this was,
maybe, but not like that out of love.
Yes, I am not asking for love, I am purely for some kind of
human perception and
communication.
Yes,
and absolutely everything that you just
told me, being an adult, conscious,
mature person, accomplished,
consciously,
I am a thirty-year-old
girl,
but I am a well-developed girl.
I see a psychologist who has worked on it.  I can
tell you that, you know,
when you are happy inside,
you don’t see all this nightmare.
Yes,
there are different aspects.  I could have lost a
friend, I lost a friend.
But if you asked me the question as a
person to a person:
"Do I choose this?"  No.  Did I vote for
this?  No.
No.  I understand.  I took part in
this.
No, I feel
sorry.  Yes, I feel sorry for your women,
children, men.  We
don't have any normal men left either.  They
come back to us,
they scream here, they kill people.  They are like this
.
Horror.  And you meet a guy, he seems
normal, but in your dream he just
beats you up in your sleep, because he’s at war and
he’s killing you.
Horror.
And I can tell you that now
you are enjoying what was said.
Yes, I wanted to hide it, but it didn’t
work, honestly.
No, you can't hide it.  But you must
understand, for example, your wife,
sister, mother, children, they did not
choose this, they are not to blame for this.
But if you have children, God forbid a
daughter, and suddenly, years later, she falls in love with a
Russian, shell-shocked after the war, and
oh, and you won’t influence it.
You know what love and a
person’s choice are, and she will follow him here,
run away here to Russia.  And if this is how
your daughter is beaten in a dream,
will you be just as happy?
I think as a man I will have to
make sure that this idiot can’t even have
contact with my daughter.  There are a ton of
cool ways to, you know, uh,
help him relax so that he, uh,
no longer has the opportunity to
think about anything at all in this life.  Understand?
Well, you get the idea.  The gist of it is this.  Well, you
need to raise your daughter properly.  That
is, look,
okay, no, you did everything right.   For
example, this Russian guy,
he looks a bit like you, and she
looks you in the eyes and says: "Dad, he's just like
you. He's just as
caring. He's just as good, he
loves me just as much as you do. It's
just awful. I almost burst into tears."
And he will tell you: “Either you accept it,
or that’s it, we will never be together again
.”  Now I
will receive him in such a way that, in short, he
will go there to the Apostle Paul.
Even if you do nothing, your
daughter will despise you.  You killed the love of her
life.   That's it
, that's it, yes, I killed him and that's it.
Well, who benefits from this?  Listen, look,
you see, if I'm ready for the sake of the burning
Kremlin, you, yes, a Russian woman, well, excuse me
for such expressions, but I consider
a Russian woman, yes, that's what I need, in short,
some Vasya, well,
well, if you're such an inveterate
Ukrainian, why don't you
speak Ukrainian?   It's
very simple, because you don't understand
Ukrainian, you know?
And you will understand what I’m going to say now.
Bachitel, what do you think?   They
bachili, they took it to clean it.  Eat, do you want to
climb out?
What else did she say?
Did you see the eyes that took it?
Wait, are
you telling me that my grandmother
said such phrases to me not in Kuban,
but in Ukrainian?   Yes.
Because the population of Kuban and
Stavropol are people from Ukraine,
who were resettled there by Russia.
Why do you despise me then?
Because you are Russian.
So I already know something in yours.
And what?  And Putin can say something in my language
?  And what?
You see, I don’t have any aversion to
Russians.  I have disgust towards
Russian citizens.  For example, a Russian
girl, a citizen of Ukraine, normal.
I had a relationship with a Russian woman from
Ukraine.  I had a relationship with a
Jewish woman from Ukraine.
Wait, I asked you a little earlier if
you've ever had a
relationship with a Russian woman?
And I'm probably not on good terms with Russia.
I misunderstood.
And now you've let it slip that this girl has done
even more damage.
Look, let's spread it out a little.  I have a
completely normal attitude towards Russians.
No, if they are from Ukraine and so on, but
as for Russians, whether they are Ukrainians from Russia,
or Russians from Russia, or Tatars from
Russia, yes, I have a negative attitude.  Well,
you see, I don’t have, I talked
to a psychiatrist, I don’t have any, in
the middle of Ukraine, either it’s Russian, or it’s
Jewish, my
wife has been divorced for a
long time, about
three years.
Why?   My
wife was Russian.
Well, she said that she wants to get a
Russian passport.  Yes, I said: “Then we’ll get a
divorce and I’ll get a passport.”
What about men, Russians?
Somehow it doesn't attract me.
You have a grudge against women.  And you have a
grudge either towards your ex-
girlfriend, or towards your ex-wife.  And here
the question is different.  The psychiatrist is trying to squeeze money out of you
, but I can
identify this boiling point and eliminate
it in one call.  The question is different.
What is this unspoken thing
you have that has become a
trigger?  This trigger has grown into
hatred towards everyone.
Yes, look, this omission is somewhere in
my head.  The psychiatrist
dug her up a little.  It arose somewhere in the
psychiatric hospital
and somewhere in the twenty-second year.  He can't
understand.  Well, I went somewhere in
1922,
right?
excavated in the twenty-second year.
Look, yes, something happened to me in
February of 1924 that made
me start to hate.
What happened before this?
Before this, something happened:
betrayal, scandal, resentment,
misunderstanding, separation.  What?
Yes, I'll explain.  This means a violation of the
Minsk and Budapest agreements.
How does this affect you?
Well, something like that, right?
How does this affect your relationship,
woman?
Well, somehow, you see, look, uh, women from
Russia started bombing my country.
Women from Russia sit and are just as afraid
as your country.
Horror.   And it is the
men and Putin who are bombing.
Understood.
We're diving into the masculine side.  Women have
nothing to do with it.   It has
nothing to do with it.  A Russian woman has started to
bombard your heart and,
apparently, your brain.  And let's return to
this.
Wait, wait.  So you want to
say that women from Russia, yes, do not
support men who
go to the front.  Women from Russia
do not collect volunteer help.
You also have Ukrainian women who are
waiting for their husbands, who they are, yes, but they are
defending their country.  The difference between
these women.  What are we doing?   Are
you attacking Ukraine?
You're laughing your ass off.  And who attacked the warehouses of Valberis
?  Razbo.
This is our answer to you.  Right.  And
fold it.   I
asked questions of your
drug addict president.  Did you ask?   Yes.  Yes.
Edal
and an order from our president.  You would have
sat down, licked him and said:
"No, I told him, I literally
had 10 seconds there with him."  I told him:
"E".
So, when he shook my hand, I
said: "Eh,
you say he shouldn't have you, he should
n't have us."  You attacked us, we are
giving you back, do you understand?  We give
you back.   They
attacked.  Why?  Because Zelensky didn't
want to negotiate amicably.
How?  About what?  Tell me, as a psychologist, what was it that
Zelensky didn’t want to agree on?
[sighs]
First of all, Zelensky is a clown.   Yes.  What does it
attack with?  Those who
make decisions stand, he decides nothing.   Yes.   Yes.
Well, he's our jester.  Look, we
Ukrainians have chosen.
Yes, we have chosen.  I don't want to talk about
it.
What are you convinced about? No?  Stop.  As a psychologist
, you said that you will now switch over and
burn.
I can figure it out.   Do
n't cut yourself off.  Look, I have no right to
talk about politics.
Why don't you have the right?  You just
said something about politics,
because I don't understand it.  I am a
victim, just like you.  Your
people, right?  If you are a victim, don't think.
Where did you run away to?  Oh yeah, look how we
unpacked it.  Beautiful.  Yes, she does.
Uh, how is that?  They didn't get together, but she
says it's because Zelensky didn't want to
negotiate, because he's a drug addict, yes,
how mean they are,
yes, they play innocent aunties who
just, yes, they suffer from
burning wildfires, a drone flies over her
apartment.  In.  Well, when it comes to the fact
that it was you who attacked Ukraine and it all
starts because your Zelensky, he’s a
clown, he’s a jester, he didn’t want to
negotiate, this devil
woke up in her, and tell me, can
you really be attracted to Russian women?  I have
only disgust.  As
Taras Shevchenko said: "Kohai from
Chornobrow is a secret from."  The same from
Moscow.  Give us a like, subscribe, and comment.
It was a divine roast.
Subscribe to our WhatsApp channel, here is the
QR code.  There, news
similar to that in the Telegram channel is posted
for those who don’t have Telegram or who don’t
use it for other reasons.
Subscribe to our WhatsApp channel.